Mss.B.H334
American Philosophical Society
- Papers, 1.75 lin. feet 4 upright boxes, 1 volume
  - Walsh, Robert to Isaac Hays, undated; Mss.B.H334
    May.
  - Warner, Langdon, undated; Mss.B.H334
    To the heirs of Henriette Hays. Thanks for a gift of a saucepan, c. 1721, to the Pennsylvania Museum and School of Industrial Art.
  - Warner, William R. to I. Minis Hays, 1882-undated; Mss.B.H334.1
    4 items: 1882 Dec. 22, 23, 26; undated
  - Warren, Edward to Isaac Hays, 1838 Sep. 14; Mss.B.H334
  - Warren, John C. to Isaac Hays, 1833-1848; Mss.B.H334
    11 items: 1833 Nov. 18, 1836 Apr. 27, 1837 May 18, 1838 Aug. 25, 1840 Apr. 13, 1846 Apr. 10, 1846 May 5, 1846 May 28, 1847 Mar. 15, 1848 Mar. 21, 1848 Jul. 5
    1967 525ms (1836 Apr. 27, 1838 Aug. 25, 1846 Apr. 10, 1846 May 28, 1846 May 5, 1847 Mar. 15, 1848 Mar. 21), 1967 940ms (1833 Nov. 18, 1837 May 18, 1840 Apr. 13, 1848 Jul. 5)
  - Warren, John C. to Isaac Hays, 1849-undated; Mss.B.H334
    12 items: 1849 Feb. 16, 1849 Feb. 26, 1849 Feb. 27, 1849 May 9, 1849 May 19, 1849 Sep. 6, 1850 Jan. 7, 1850 Jan. 31, 1850 Feb. 4, 1855 Feb. 2, 1855 May 12, undated Jun. 9
    1967 525ms (1850 Feb. 4, 1850 Jan. 31, 1850 Jan. 7, 1855 Feb. 2, undated Jun. 9), 1967 562ms (1849 Feb. 26, 1849 Feb. 27, 1855 May 12), 1967 940ms (1849 Feb. 16, 1849 May 19, 1849 May 9, 1849 Sep. 6)
  - Warren, J. Mason to Isaac Hays, 1846-undated; Mss.B.H334
    1967 525ms, 940ms (1849)
    5 items: 1846 Feb. 1, 1847 Dec. 17, 1848 Jan. 20, 1849 May 25, undated May 25
  - Warren, Mason J.
    Unlocated June 2011. Possible J. Mason Warren.
  - Welch, William Henry to I. Minis Hays, 1901 Apr. 29; Mss.B.H334.1
  - Wernerian Natural History Society of Edinburgh to Isaac Hays, 1835 Mar. 1; Mss.B.H334
  - West, Charles to Isaac Hays, 1850 Apr. 1; Mss.B.H334
  - White, Thomas W. to Isaac Hays, 1967 940ms; Mss.B.H334
  - Wiesner, Wilson Reynolds to I. Minis Hays, 1909 Nov. 18; Mss.B.H334.1
  - Wilkes, Charles, undated; Mss.B.H334
    August 21.
  - Wilkes, George to Isaac Hays, 1842 Dec. 21; Mss.B.H334
  - Williams, H. I., undated; Mss.B.H334
    September 30.
  - Winslow, Forbes to Isaac Hays, 1850-1857; Mss.B.H334
    2 items: 1850 Oct. 26, 1857 May 4
  - Witmer, Emma R. to I. Minis Hays, 1908 Oct. 30; Mss.B.H334.1
  - Woakes, Edward to Isaac Hays, 1878 Feb. 19; Mss.B.H334
  - Wood, Emma, 1858 Aug. 1; Mss.B.H334
    To "My dear cousin," detailing travel.
  - Wood, George Bacon, 1848-1853; Mss.B.H334
    1967 525m (1853), 940ms (1848)
    2 items: 1848 Jun. 14, 1853 May 6
  - Wood, Grace A. to I. Minis Hays, 1922 Feb. 24; Mss.B.H334.1
  - Wyman, J. to Isaac Hays, 1852 Jul. 22; Mss.B.H334
  - Wyman, M. to Isaac Hays, 1848 Jun. 8; Mss.B.H334